如果你告诉别人这件事的话 我就会泄露你的小秘密
If you tell anyone I am, I will release your secrets.
听着 我们知道你希望你的女儿
Look, we know you want your daughter
为你的工作感到骄傲
to be proud of the work that you do.
我只是希望你知道你对99分局有多重要
I just hope you know how important you've been to the Nine-Nine.
对 就今天 我终于能掏出搜查令
Yeah, just today, I was able to pull a warrant
并且逮捕了一个我追踪了三个月的人
and arrest the guy I've been tracking for three months
就是因为你解决了网络问题
because you got the internet back.
你是不可或缺的
You're indispensible
我们真的会很想念你
and we're really gonna miss you.
我也很爱99分局 伙伴们
And I loved the Nine-Nine, you guys.
就是感觉是时候去
It just feels like it's time for me
建造一些属于我自己的东西了
to, like, build something of my own.
就像我的创业偶像
Like my entrepreneurial idols,
奥普拉·温弗莉 还有莱克斯·卢瑟
Oprah Winfrey, Lex Luthor...
那个里的反派吗
The Superman villain?
他建立了自己的帝国 不是吗
He built an empire, didn't he?